<resources>
    <string name="app_name">lab2</string>
    <string name="article_title">7 Skills All C.E.Os should Master</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle"><i>Here are some skills all C.E.O must master</i></string>
    <string name="article_text">Everyone wants the corner office with the great view, but not everyone has the same skills to get there. Becoming CEO is more than just “what you know,” and “who you know,” The qualities that make a great CEO are actually a compilation of a lot of things top-level executives master on their own.
    \nFor more information see the article at https://www.alux.com/skills-ceos/
    \n\n
    <b>1. Diplomacy</b>
    \n\n
    \tThey don\’t teach you this stuff in college. Right, so what is diplomacy, exactly\? Diplomacy is the \“art of dealing with people in a sensitive and tactful way.\”\n
    \tAs CEO, this is a skill that will serve you well for your entire career. By being diplomatic, your staff will be assured of your ability to diffuse situations with the utmost tact and fairness, and they won\’t feel like you\’re playing favourites or have a particular loyalty to certain staff members.\n
    \tAs former US Ambassador to the UN, Richard Holbrooke said, \“Diplomacy is like jazz: endless variations on a theme.\” As CEO, your approach to diplomacy will also constantly be changing, so it\’s a skill you\’ll need to keep on top of.
    \n\n
    <b>2. Vision and Follow Through</b>
    \n\n
    \tThat\’s the difference between CEO material and well… non-CEO material. It’s the vision coupled with follow through. And let\’s not forget to add a dash of risk too, because following through on a vision always comes with a side of riskiness.
    \n\n
    <b>3. Passion for Their Job and its People</b>
    \n\n
    \tIt\’s no secret, CEOs make a lot of money. We chatted extensively about it in our video, How CEOs Make 351x More Money. In the video we answer integral questions like why pay them so much, and are they worth it\?
    \n
    \tAnd while we\’ve all worked for horrendous CEOs, working for a CEO who is passionate about their work, their company and its people is an incredible experience – and that\’s a skill that all successful CEOs should have.
    \n\n
    <b>4. Brevity</b>
    \n\n
    \tIt\’s a word that just flows off the tongue and it means: writing or speaking in a short, concise, clear manner.
    \n
    \tForbes published an article titled, \"Half Of All Meetings Are A Waste Of Time.\" A skilled CEO would not call meetings that would waste their employees time, and leverage their brevity when communicating with staff.
    \n\n
    <b>5. Decisiveness</b>
    \n\n
    \tCanadian motivational speaker, Brian Tracey once said, \“Decisiveness is a characteristic of high-performing men and women. Almost any decision is better than no decision at all.\”
    \n
    <i>
Nobody can become CEO if they can\’t make decisions.</i>
    \n\n
    <b>6. Accountability</b>
    \n\n
    \tAs suggested by rightattitudes.com \“A true leader doesn\’t pass the blame for failure, but graciously accepts responsibility for the problems he inherited.
    \n
    According to CEO World, A CEO not being accountable doesn\’t just look bad, it leads to further breakdown, like:\n
    <ul>Giving Away your power</ul>
    <ul>Creating a toxic environment</ul>
    <ul>Employee disengagement</ul>
    <ul>Reduced productivity</ul>
    <ul>You’re perceived as being an incapable leader.</ul>
    \n\n
    <b>7. Controlled Emotion</b>
    \n\n
    \tWhen the pawpaw hits the fan, or times are stressful, you can\’t have a CEO dramatically shoving laptops and paperwork all over the floor, declaring it’s \“F*ck this S*it O Clock…\”
    \n
    \tNope, you need a level-headed, calm individual who isn’t going to explode and lose their cool.
    \n
    \tHealthline.com has some solid, achievable advice for this – they say, when it comes to emotions, best to \“… aim for regulation, not repression.\”

    </string>

</resources>